# **Summary**

Hi! I'm Felipe Monteiro

— a music producer
and sound designer
with over 5 years of
study and practices in
the field.

My most recent project involved producing an EP from scratch as a service for another artist - composition, production, recording of vocals, mixing and mastering.

Currently based in São Paulo, Brazil.

# **Experience**

## **ThayB**

Single & EP production · October 2023 - Ongoing

- Composing and producing the instrumentals
- Vocal recording sessions
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

### yLLop - Personal Project

Singles, EP & LP · June 2021 - Ongoing

- Composing and producing the songs
- Synthesis of electronic elements
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

### **Discos & Girafas**

Podcast production · October 2020 - July 2022

- Recording of the raw material
- Audio editing & FX
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

## **Education**

## Anhembi Morumbi

Music Production January 2023 - December 2024

# **ETEC Getulio Vargas**

High School & Technician January 2012 - December 2014

### **Details**

# **Felipe** de Carvalho **Monteiro**

### **Portfolio**

yllopmusic.vercel.app

#### **Email**

yllopmusic@gmail.com felipe0597@hotmail.com

### Phone

+55 11 96361 4921

### **Skills**

### Music / Audio

Music Theory · Sound Design · Synthesis · Mixing · Mastering · Sample Manipulation · Editing · FX Chain

### **Tools**

FL Studio · Pro Tools · Xfer Serum · Figma · Premiere · After Effects

### Languages

- Portuguese (native)
- English (advanced)
- Spanish (basic)
- · Japanese (basic)